intellectsoft.net 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Intellectsoft US

We respect our website visitors and the confidentiality of personal information provided by the visitors to our website. Please read the following privacy policy, with which you give your consent to the collection, storage and usage of information about you in accordance with this policy.

**How we use your information?**

We collect information for the following purposes:

• to analyze your needs;

• to improve our services;

• to show you advertisements on our products/services, special offers.

**How we collect information about you?**

We use the cookie-files in order to collect general information about visitors.

Cookies are small files, which a website with your permission sends via the web browser to your computer’s hard drive. It enables the site to recognize your browser, collect and store information about you.

Cookie-files allow us to store and process information about your visits to our website to recognize your preferences for future visits, to collect general information about traffic and website interaction.

**Denial of responsibility**

You can accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your settings and completely disable your browser to all cookie files.

This website may contain links to other websites. We, in turn, are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read carefully the privacy policies of each site which collects personal information about the user.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at the following address [info@www.intellectsoft.net](mailto:info@www.intellectsoft.net)
